<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Software Testing Trends]]></title><description><![CDATA[A starter blog demonstrating what Gatsby can do.]]></description><link>https://softwaretestingtrends.com</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2020 01:25:13 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[Roadmap to become Test Automation Engineer!]]></title><description><![CDATA[If you are Software Testing Professionals & want to learn skills to be the one who can automate the boring, repetitive and time consuming…]]></description><link>https://softwaretestingtrends.com/my-second-post/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://softwaretestingtrends.com/my-second-post/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2020 15:38:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;If you are Software Testing Professionals &amp;#x26; want to learn skills to be the one who can automate the boring, repetitive and time consuming software testing tasks then this course will provide you the road map to start your journey.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don’t get overwhelmed by the large number of information and automation technologies that are available in the market. Follow this course and define your clear path to become Automation developer/engineer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.udemy.com/course/road-map-to-become-test-automation-engineer/?referralCode=0CF887F5712A3306049F&quot;&gt;You can get my Udemy Course here&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- #1: Embed through web URL --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;gatsby-resp-iframe-wrapper&quot; style=&quot;padding-bottom: 50%; position: relative; height: 0; overflow: hidden; margin-bottom: 1.0725rem&quot; &gt; &lt;div class=&quot;embedVideo-container&quot;&gt; &lt;iframe title src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/HWMd-0K2LH8?rel=0&quot; class=&quot;embedVideo-iframe&quot; style=&quot;border:0; position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; &quot; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- #2: Embed through video ID --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;gatsby-resp-iframe-wrapper&quot; style=&quot;padding-bottom: 50%; position: relative; height: 0; overflow: hidden; margin-bottom: 1.0725rem&quot; &gt; &lt;div class=&quot;embedVideo-container&quot;&gt; &lt;iframe title src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/UJ6PmaCMsBA?rel=0&quot; class=&quot;embedVideo-iframe&quot; style=&quot;border:0; position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; &quot; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enjoyed watching the video, nice and simple and easy to learn. (Sam Rigby)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a great starting point for someone looking to transition to automation. The presenter was lively and engaging and this made absorbing the information easy. The instruction and showcasing step by step was helpful and informative. I’d recommend this course to newbies. (supaflyii)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Clear and concise,It has given me knowledge on testing. (Shriya Raj Malpe)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Unit Tests Vs End To End Tests]]></title><description><![CDATA[The objective of both testing types is different. The purpose of unit testing is to create a robust codebase. This also allows to identify…]]></description><link>https://softwaretestingtrends.com/hello-world/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://softwaretestingtrends.com/hello-world/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 22:12:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;The objective of both testing types is different. The purpose of unit testing is to create a robust codebase. This also allows to identify the defects very early in the software lifecycle (Shift Left). Unit Tests makes up the largest section of the pyramid, therefore creating a sold base.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;E2E tests are typically slow because they run against the GUI, interacting with the real server, acting like a real user. They need a working application. That’s why E2E tests are not feasible to be used as the only/main test type. They are pretty important because they are testing everything but they must be used carefully to avoid brittle and time consuming test suites.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Having no or fewer unit tests &amp;#x26; more E2E tests is an anti-pattern. Martin Fowler and others within the engineering, QA and DevOps communities call it as ice-cream cone effect.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This &lt;a href=&quot;https://testing.googleblog.com/2015/04/just-say-no-to-more-end-to-end-tests.html&quot;&gt;Google Testing Blog&lt;/a&gt; also expands on why you shouldn’t rely on end-to-end tests.   &lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>